<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Udgam 2019</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Udgam 2019</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">udgam.nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_udgam">About Udgam</string>
    <string name="sponsors">Sponsors</string>
    <string name="developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log-Out</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="guests">Guests</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate App</string>
    <string name="udgam_team">Udgam Team</string>
    <string name="application">Application</string>
    <string name="udgam">Udgam 2019</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event">EventActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed">tabbed</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="line_1">Line 1</string>
    <string name="line_2">Line 2</string>


    <string name="tug_of_war">Tug of War</string>
    <string name="face_painting">Face Painting</string>
    <string name="debate">Debate</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt">Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b">Heart To Heart And Brain To Brain</string>
    <string name="wall_painting">Wall Painting</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight">Balloon Fight</string>
    <string name="super_over">Super Over</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling">Arm Wrestling</string>
    <string name="antakshri">Antakshari</string>
    <string name="just_a_minute">Just A Minute(JAM)</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale">Twist A Tale</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off">Dance Face-Off</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion">Switching Emotion</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="alfaaz">Alfaaz</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz">Dumb Charades</string>
    <string name="open_mic">Open Mic</string>
    <string name="high_voltage">High Voltage</string>
    <string name="pubg">PUBG</string>
    <string name="counter_strike">Counter Strike</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi">Camera Ne Bana Di Jodi</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest">Short Film Contest</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk">Ramp Walk</string>
    <string name="nit_idol">NIT Idol</string>
    <string name="tiger_five">Tiger Five</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_description">EventDescriptionActivity</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules and Regulations</string>

    <string name="quiz_name1">Abhishek Kumar</string>
    <string name="quiz_name1_email">b170114@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="quiz_name1_phone">+91-9939532732</string>
    <string name="quiz_name2">Pawan Kumar</string>
    <string name="quiz_name2_email">b170151@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="quiz_name2_phone">+91-9494802251</string>
    <string name="quiz_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="quiz_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="quiz_description">1. The quiz will have two rounds, Screening Round and Stage Rounds.

\n\n2. Only team entries are eligible and a team shall consist of 2 members.

\n\n3. A screening round will be conducted to shortlist minimum 6 teams from the pool of registered teams, for the stage rounds.

\n\n4. The decision of the quiz organizing committee will be final and will not be subjected to any change in case.

\n\n5. The use of mobile or any other information retrieval system is strictly system is strictly prohibited.

\n\n6. Replacement of any team member is not allowed after registration.

\n\n7. The rules of the stage rounds will be disclosed later.
</string>

    <string name="debate_name1">Alok Kumar Tripathi</string>
    <string name="debate_name1_email">b170081@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="debate_name1_phone">+91-9680053598</string>
    <string name="debate_name2">Tanushree</string>
    <string name="debate_name2_email">b170073@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="debate_name2_phone">+91-9424064098</string>
    <string name="debate_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="debate_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="debate_description">A debate, where every opinion will be given a stage and every belief will be established. Prove your take on the topic by using witty remarks and slaying each others opinion.

\n\nRULES:\n\n1. Each team shall consist of two members.
\n\n2. The competition will consist of several levels and each level will have different segments.
\n\n3. In the first segment each team will be given a time of 3 minutes in which the team will present and elaborate their points.
\n\n4. The team supposed to speak in motion will be the one to introduce the topic and elaborate their views as to why they are favouring the motion.
\n\n5. The team opposing the motion will be the next to speak for three minutes.
\n\n6. Next segment will be of 5 minutes of affirmations and rebuttals between the favoring and opposing teams.
\n\n7. In the end the jury and audience will be asking questions to the debaters.
\n\n8. Topics will be given a day before the event, but favor or motion will be decided on the spot by lottery system.
\n\nJudging Criteria
    \n\nLanguage proficiency
\n\nContent relevance
\n\nBody language
\n\nFluency
\n\nAnswers given in questioning segment</string>

    <string name="tug_of_war_name1">Kabita Chhetri</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_name1_email">b170017@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_name1_phone">+91-7551012390</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_name2">Sandeep Gupta</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_name2_email">b170141@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_name2_phone">+91-9838397181</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_place">NIT Sikkim Ground</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_description">STRENGTH? REALLY?
\n\nA contest in which two teams pull at opposite end of rope until one drags the other over the central line.
        \n\n1. Each team consists of 8 members and 2 substitutes.
\n\n2. The rope must be pulled underarm and nobody’s elbow must go below the knee otherwise a foul will be called.
        \n\n3. No knots or loops shall be made in the rope, nor shall it be locked                across any part of the body of any member of the team.
     \n\n4. In case any team found breaking the rules would be disqualified.
 \n\n5. Both teams pull the rope, the winner being the team who manage   to pull the mark on the rope closest to their opponents over the center line.
\n\n6. Matches are often a best of 3 pull, the winner winning 2 out of the 3 pulls.
\n\n7. Tournament will be conducted on knock-out basis.
    \n\n*NOTE
    \n\nIn case of any argument, committee decision would be considered as final decision.</string>

    <string name="face_painting_name1">Sameer Choubey</string>
    <string name="face_painting_name1_email">b170095@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="face_painting_name1_phone">+91-9983522351</string>
    <string name="face_painting_name2">Priya Kumari Prasad</string>
    <string name="face_painting_name2_email">b170122@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="face_painting_name2_phone">+91-9832470123</string>
    <string name="face_painting_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="face_painting_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="face_painting_description">Get some new shades up your face. Trust the man with the brush in hand and wait for colours to create magic.
        \n\n1. A team should be composed of 2 members.
\n\n2. Colours, brushes etc will be provided organizers.
\n\n3. Time limit is 150 minutes.
\n\n4. Participants must come up with a good theme.
\n\n5. Decision of the judges will be final and binding.</string>

    <string name="treasure_hunt_name1">Ankita Singh</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_name1_email">b170030@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_name1_phone">+91-9934944900</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_name2">Nishi Kumari</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_name2_email">b170105@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_name2_phone">+91-9614811076</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="treasure_hunt_description">A clue will be provided to each team, following that clue remaining clues need to be found out.
        \n\n1. Each team consists of 4 and not more than 7 members.
\n\n2. There are total 4 clues and the final destination (treasure) will be same for all the teams.
\n\n3. Time provided for finding all clue is one hour.
\n\n4. There will be 2 rounds. After 1st round top 8 teams will be selected.
 \n\n5. Selection will be based on time taken and if all clues are found in sequence and at right place.
\n\n6. Maximum 32 teams can participate and participation will be based on First come First serve basis.
\n\n7. If any team is found picking the clues of other team, that team will be eliminated.
\n\n8. In case of argument, committee decision will be final.
    </string>

    <string name="h2hb2b_name1">Tanushree</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_name1_email">b170073@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_name2">Priya Kumari Prasad</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_name2_email">b170122@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_name2_phone">+91-9832470123</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="h2hb2b_description">Do you think you have a strong bond with your friend? Let\’s put this bond to test and explore how much you know about each other through some super exciting questions. And guess what? You’ll know towards the end of road how firm your connections are.

\n\nRULES:
\n\n1. This event will be conducted in 2 separate rooms.
\n\n2. Team of 2 people would be requested to participate.
\n\n3. Participants in this event will be seated in different rooms and will be needed to answer same questions about themselves and other person.
\n\n4. Team with maximum no. of same answers will win.
    </string>

    <string name="wall_painting_name1">Kabita Chhetri</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_name1_email">b170017@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_name1_phone">+91-7551012390</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_name2">Rajani Kumari</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_name2_email">b170132@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_name2_phone">+91-9564498405</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="wall_painting_description">“Art is anything you can get away with.” - ANDY WARHOL
Turn your imagination into reality by portraying your art through wall painting competition.
        \n\n1. Group registration should preferably be done online before the start of event.
\n\n2. Participants should get their designs verified by sending scanned copy of it to b170017@nitsikkim.ac.in .
\n\n3. The painting should be made according to the theme provided.
\n\n4. THEME: COMIC CULTURE. (you can contact the respective organizers if the description for the theme is needed.)
\n\n5. On spot entries are allowed but verification of design needs to be done from the event coordinator before painting on wall.
\n\n6. Organizers will provide materials for painting.
\n\n7. The wall dimensions will be informed to the teams registering for event.
\n\n8. The team should not exceed more than five members.</string>

    <string name="balloon_fight_name1">Rohit Ranjan</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_name1_email">b170118@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_name1_phone">+91-8092084102</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_name2">Pawan Verma</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_name2_email">b170061@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_name2_phone">+91-9919906259</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_place">Cricket Ground</string>
    <string name="balloon_fight_description">1. No. of paint balls (water balloons filled with organic colour) will be limited for each team.
\n\n2. Players must never hit one another physically.
\n\n3. Once the balloon splashes on your body, you are eliminated (for that round).
\n\n4. Game will be held in 3 rounds (on cricket ground).
\n\n5. Each team will consist of 5 members.

        \n\nRound 1:
\n\nCapture the flag
\n\n1. Each of the two teams has a flag in their base, which are located on opposite sides of the game zone. The aim of the game is to capture the enemy\’s flag from their base and deliver it back to your base before they capture your flag. The flags cannot be removed or hidden by the team that is guarding it.
\n\n2. The team that delivers the flag first wins.
\n\nRound 2:
\n\nBomb the base
\n\n1. tOne team starts off with a "Bomb" (decided on basis of toss).To Make the way to the opposing team\'s base will be the task for the team with the bomb.
\n\n2. *He/she must leave the bomb in that position and either team can then obtain it and advance it to the opposing team\'s base when the player is shot. 
\n\n3. Round ends when either side is eliminated, or the bomb reaches the destination.

        \n\nFinal round:
\n\nProtect the President
\n\n1. One member from the defending team is nominated to be the president who has to be protected and possibly escorted to safety by the rest of the team. The objective of the attacking team is to take down the president before the game is over.
    </string>

    <string name="super_over_name1">Abhinesh Sharma</string>
    <string name="super_over_name1_email">b170076@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="super_over_name1_phone">+91-9828916458</string>
    <string name="super_over_name2">Viraj Diwakar</string>
    <string name="super_over_name2_email">b170113@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="super_over_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="super_over_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="super_over_place">Cricket Ground</string>
    <string name="super_over_description">If you are a passionate lover of cricket then come and participate in the game.
        \n\n1. The competition will consists a cricket match of one over(each inning).
\n\n2. Each team will consist of 5 members.
\n\n3. Each side has to decide on who three players will bat, meaning that the loss of two wickets ends the super over.
\n\n4. There will be one free hit in each inning but can\'t be taken on last ball.
\n\n5. The run made on the last ball will get double.
\n\n6. There will be league matches.
    \n\n\nWINNING CRITERIA:
\n\nIf the super over ends in tie, the first satisfied of the following criteria\'s will determine the winner:
\n\n1. The team with the most boundaries will be the winner.
\n\n2. If both teams have same number of boundaries then the winner will be decided by a toss.
    </string>

    <string name="arm_wrestling_name1">Abhishek Ranjan</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_name1_email">b1700142@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_name1_phone">+91-8145225531</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_name2">Nishi</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_name2_email">b170105@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_name2_phone">+91-8001495848</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="arm_wrestling_description">1. The competitors should approach the table, make themselves comfortable and then grip their opponent\'s hand. The grip should be palm to palm with the thumb knuckle visible. Their other hands should grip their respective hand peg.
        \n\n2. The Competitors have one minute to “grip up” if in that time, they have not gripped up, they will be given a “referee\'s grip”.
\n\n3. Once the referees are happy with the grip from both competitors, the contest will begin. Each competitor should attempt to pin their opponent\'s arm onto the touch pad.
\n\n4. Pressure should be in a sideways capacity to force their opponent\'s hand to the touch pad. Back pressure in an attempt to drag the opponent off toward the centre of the table is not allowed.
\n\n5. The match is won when one competitor pins their opponent\'s hand onto the touch pad. At this point, if the head referee agrees that it is a valid pin, he/she will be the winner.
    /n/n*Foul:
\n\nCompetitors shoulders must not cross the “centre line” between pegs during competition.
\n\nThey can\’t drop the competing shoulder below the level of the elbow pad when in a neutral or losing position.
\n\nThe competitor\’s elbow should not loose contact with elbow pad.
    \n\n**Note
    \n\nTwo warnings will be considered as one foul and two foul results in disqualification of an opposite participant.
    </string>

    <string name="antakshri_name1">Vicky Kumar</string>
    <string name="antakshri_name1_email">b170040@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="antakshri_name1_phone">+91-9680098246</string>
    <string name="antakshri_name2">Rimjhim Kumari</string>
    <string name="antakshri_name2_email">b170041@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="antakshri_name2_phone">+91-9462254971</string>
    <string name="antakshri_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="antakshri_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="antakshri_description">1. There will be total 4 rounds.
\n\n2. The rounds will be revealed on the spot.
\n\n3. Only Hindi songs are allowed in any round.
\n\n4. No song should be repeated in the same round.
\n\n5. However, you can sing the same song from any of the previous rounds.
\n\n6. For each correct response, you will get 10 points.
\n\n7. For each wrong or no response 5 points will be deducted.
\n\n8. If the team is not able to respond the turn will be passed to the next team.
\n\n9. Each team will have 4 players.
\n\n10. The decisions of the judges will be final and binding.
    </string>

    <string name="jam_name1">Alok Kumar Tripathi</string>
    <string name="jam_name1_email">b170081@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="jam_name1_phone">+91-9680053598</string>
    <string name="jam_name2">Tanushree</string>
    <string name="jam_name2_email">b170073@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="jam_name2_phone">+91-9424064098</string>
    <string name="jam_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="jam_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="jam_description">It’s time to give those long sighs a meaning, all blurry ideas a canvas and an audience to all those trembling words on the most exciting topics. YES!! You have got a single minute to wear your heart on your sleeves and bare yourself open.
\n\nRULES:\n\n1. Topics will be instantly provided at the spot on lottery basis.
\n\n2. You will be given 3 minutes to think about it.
\n\n3. You have to speak for a minute.
\n\n4. Judging will be done on the basis of content, fluency and confidence.
</string>

    <string name="twist_a_tale_name1">Ayush Raj</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_name1_email">b170185@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_name1_phone">+91-9504378653</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_name2">Pawan Kumar</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_name2_email">b170151@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_name2_phone">+91-9494802251</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="twist_a_tale_description">Ever felt that some stories could have different beginnings, middles or endings if they were written in this age? Put on your thinking caps, get witty, humorous or sarcastic. Take up a story and give it a twist. UDGAM is giving you an opportunity to showcase your creative talent and leave us in awe that the plot could have been thus framed.
        \n\n1. Initials of the plot will be given to the participant beforehand.
\n\n2. Each participant will be given a time limit of 5 minutes to frame the story.
\n\n3. Participants need to narrate their story at least  for 3 minutes.
\n\n4. 4.Your twist should be believable and should make sense.
\n\n5. No story should be framed in accordance to any pre-heard tale.
\n\n6. Judgement will be based on your narration and conclusion of story.</string>

    <string name="dance_face_off_name1">Sunny Kumar</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_name1_email">b170120@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_name1_phone">+91-9852211257</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_name2">Priya Kumari Prasad</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_name2_email">b170122@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_name2_phone">+91-9832470123</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="dance_face_off_description">Dance faceoff is basically a dance competition between two groups (or individuals) at a time.
Performance may be solo or in group.
        \n\nRules:\n\n1. In a group maximum 3 members are allowed.
        \n\n2. Song duration: 2 minutes.
\n\n3. Every round will be the elimination round, so after each round one of the group will be eliminates.
\n\n4. Same step should not be repeated again and again.
\n\n5. Boys and girls may remain in a single group.
\n\n6. Song choice must be given by event management team member.
\n\n7. The decision of Judges will be final and binding.
</string>

    <string name="switching_emotion_name1">Ankita Singh</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_name1_email">b170030@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_name1_phone">+91-9934944900</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_name2">Rimjhim kumari</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_name2_email">b170041@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_name2_phone">+91-9462254971</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="switching_emotion_description">1. Performance time for each participant will be 2 minutes.
\n\nParticipants will have to flip 3 gestures and act accordingly.
\n\nSituation that participant have to perform will be given by judges.
\n\nPerformance will be judged on the basis of confidence, creativity, attitude and time taken.</string>

    <string name="connected_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="connected_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="connected_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="connected_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="connected_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="connected_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="connected_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="connected_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="connected_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="alfaaz_name1">Vicky Kumar</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_name1_email">b170040@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_name1_phone">+91-9680098246</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_name2">Gaurav Shukla</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_name2_email">b170077@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_description">Poetry Competition
        \n\n1. Individual entries are invited.
\n\n2. Participants should not use slangs.
\n\n3. Marks will be given on the basis of content, fluency, presentation.
\n\n4. Decision of the judges will be final and binding.</string>

    <string name="dumsharaz_name1">Ayush Raj</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_name1_email">b170185@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_name1_phone">+91-9504378653</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_name2">Rohit Ranjan</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_name2_email">b170118@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_name2_phone">+91-8092084102</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="dumsharaz_description">DUMB CHARADES: ISHARON HI ISHARON MEIN
        \n\nSpeech is silver, silence is Gold. It’s time for Action, Words are Old!
        \n\n1. Participation should come in team and every team will have 3 members.
\n\n2. The event will be organized in two rounds which are:
\n\t\t\tMovie Titles- Round1 (Time limit: 2 minutes)
\n\t\t\tMovie Song- Round2 (Time limit: 1 and half minutes)
\n\n3. Each member of the team has to come at least once for gesticulation.
\n\n4. Maximum attempts by the team members to guess will be 5.
\n\n5. Lip movement or any kind of sound is unacceptable.
\n\n6. Any word can be broken into maximum of two parts
\n\n7. Any word to be guessed should not be directly pointed out to other team members.
\n\n8. In case of any discrepancies, the decision of judges will be final and binding.</string>

    <string name="open_mic_name1">Ankita Singh</string>
    <string name="open_mic_name1_email">b170030@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="open_mic_name1_phone">+91-9934499400</string>
    <string name="open_mic_name2">Gaurav Shukla</string>
    <string name="open_mic_name2_email">b170077@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="open_mic_name2_phone">+91-7054225368</string>
    <string name="open_mic_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="open_mic_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="open_mic_description">Knock knock! Are you the best entertainer in your squad? Do your friends often die laughing at your wittiest jokes? Well, we\’ve got the stage ready for you. Grab the opportunity!

\n\nRULES AND REGULATIONS:\n\n1. Participation is for individual candidates only.
        \n\n2. This event would consist of 2 rounds. More information will be conveyed later.
\n\n3. Participants must perform their original, genuine act.
\n\n4. The maximum time allotted would be 7 minutes.
        \n\n5. Any discrimination on the basis of colour, race and caste will not be entertained. Vulgar and obscene language will disqualify the candidate immediately.
\n\n6. Marks will be awarded based on content, fluency, spontaneity, presentation and sense of humour.
\n\n7. Jury\’s decision would be final and binding.</string>

    <string name="high_voltage_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="high_voltage_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="pubg_name1">Abhishek Kumar</string>
    <string name="pubg_name1_email">b170114@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="pubg_name1_phone">+91-9939532732</string>
    <string name="pubg_name2">Pawan Verma</string>
    <string name="pubg_name2_email">b170061@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="pubg_name2_phone">+91-9919906259</string>
    <string name="pubg_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="pubg_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="pubg_description">1. GAME type: SQUAD, TPP
\n\n2. Every player must have the latest version of PUBG Mobile installed in their systems. (Both mobile and Emulator allowed).
\n\n3. Team leader registering the team must be from NIT Sikkim.
\n\n4. In game teaming up (if two squads are found to play together) would lead to the disqualification of both the squads.
\n\n5. Detailed fixture will be provided one day before the event after the closing of registrations.
\n\n6. In the fixture each team will be provided a particular team slot (will be mailed or sent to the leaders contact number), anyone occupying some other teams slot will be removed.
\n\n7. Timing of the match will be informed.
\n\n8. Any team using hacks or glitches will be disqualified for the whole tournament.
\n\n9. Any more information will be conveyed later. For more query contact organizers.
    \n\nEntry Fee INR 100 per team</string>

    <string name="counter_strike_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="counter_strike_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name1">Alok Kumar Tripathi</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name1_email">b170081@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name1_phone">+91-9680053698</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name2">Nishi Kumari</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name2_email">b170105@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_name2_phone">+91-9614811076</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="camera_ne_bana_di_jodi_description">Taking pictures is savoring the life intensely, every hundredth of a second. Life goes on, but a photograph is a momenta of that moment. A photograph has the ability to convey emotion, mood, narrative ideas and messages. This event is a platform which gives you a golden opportunity to become the best Jodi of our college NIT SIKKIM as a model and photographer. So be ready with your camera (either DSLR or mobile) and model. Capture the best pic of your model and showcase your talent.
        \n\n1. TEAM SIZE: 2 (one model and one photographer).
\n\n2. ROUND(s): One round event.
\n\n3. TYPE OF PHOTOGRAPHS TO BE SUBMITTED:
\n\t Selfie
\n\t Candid
\n\t Portrait.
\n\t Fashion photography
\n\n4. PHOTOS LIMIT: 4 (one from each category)
\n\n5. LAST DATE TO SEND ENTRIES:
\n\n6. JUDGING CRITERIA: Your photograph will be judged on the basis of composition, creativity and message.
\n\n7. GENERAL RULES:
\n\n8. Camera resolution should be at least 5MP.
\n\n9. Entries will be considered from 18th to 28th april
\n\n10. Any use of special effects like glamour glow and any frames used in photograph will not be considered.
\n\n11. Any sign of plagiarism will lead to disqualification.
\n\n12. The decision of judges or organizing committee will be final and binding.
    \n\nSUBMISSION:
\n\nYou can send your entries through mail to organizers till the last date of submission. Name and roll no. of photographer and model should be mentioned.</string>

    <string name="short_film_contest_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="short_film_contest_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="ramp_walk_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="ramp_walk_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="nit_idol_name1">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_name1_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_name1_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_name2">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_name2_email">b170088@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_name2_phone">+91-7091626749</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="nit_idol_description">descreption</string>

    <string name="tiger_five_name1">Sameer Choubey</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_name1_email">b170095@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_name1_phone">+91-9983522351</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_name2">Sanjeet Marten</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_name2_email">b170080@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_name2_phone">+91-7478978991</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_time">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_place">To be decided later</string>
    <string name="tiger_five_description">Talk With Your Feet, Play With Your Heart. There may be a Messi hiding in you.
        \n\n1. There must be 6 players a side (5 players + 1 substitute).
\n\n2. Game will have two halves. 10 minutes each.
\n\n3. Unlimited substitution will be allowed.
\n\n4. Goals from kick off is not permitted.
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_profile_bottom_sheet">Profile</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="report_bug">Report Bug</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="youtube">YouTube</string>
    <string name="web">Website</string>
    <string name="feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="write_something">Write Something</string>
    <string name="feedback_sent">Feedback Sent</string>
    <string name="other_teams">Other Teams</string>

    <string name="prateek">Prateek</string>
    <string name="prateek_full">Prateek Kumar Oraon</string>
    <string name="prateek_designation">Designer and Developer</string>
    <string name="prateek_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="prateek_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="prateek_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="prateek_git"></string>
    <string name="prateek_fb"></string>
    <string name="prateek_des">blah blah blah</string>

    <string name="prince">Prince</string>
    <string name="prince_full">Prince Raj</string>
    <string name="prince_designation">Project Head and Developer</string>
    <string name="prince_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="prince_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="prince_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="prince_git"></string>
    <string name="prince_fb"></string>
    <string name="prince_des">blah blah blah</string>

    <string name="dhrub">Dhrubajit</string>
    <string name="dhrub_full">Dhrubajit Sarkar</string>
    <string name="dhrub_designation">Developer</string>
    <string name="dhrub_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="dhrub_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="dhrub_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="dhrub_git"></string>
    <string name="dhrub_fb"></string>
    <string name="dhrub_des"></string>

    <string name="ud">Udaishya</string>
    <string name="ud_full">Udaishya Yadav</string>
    <string name="ud_designation"></string>
    <string name="ud_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="ud_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="ud_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="ud_git"></string>
    <string name="ud_fb"></string>
    <string name="ud_des"></string>

    <string name="vaibhav">Vaibhav</string>
    <string name="vaibhav_full">Vaibhav kuch hoge aage</string>
    <string name="vaibhav_designation">pata nahi</string>
    <string name="vaibhav_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="vaibhav_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="vaibhav_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="vaibhav_git"></string>
    <string name="vaibhav_fb"></string>
    <string name="vaibhav_des"></string>

    <string name="anjali">Anjali</string>
    <string name="anjali_full">Anjali bagal wale ka surname</string>
    <string name="anjali_designation">pata nahi</string>
    <string name="anjali_phone">+91-9931905946</string>
    <string name="anjali_email">b170078@nitsikkim.ac.in</string>
    <string name="anjali_linkedIn"></string>
    <string name="anjali_git"></string>
    <string name="anjali_fb"></string>
    <string name="anjali_des"></string>

    <string name="nitskm">National Institute of Technology Sikkim</string>
    <string name="about_udgam_02">UDGAM is The magnificent annual cultural fest of NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY SIKKIM, a heart-throb fest of Kanchenjunga, a complete feast for its participants and a matter of ecstasy for all its students. Offering a vivid blend of music, art, dance, talent and enthralling events of the fest, all brimming with  craziness, weirdness, wackiness and never ending entertainment. A room for roar laugh and giggle.</string>
    <string name="about_udgam_01">NIT Sikkim has been pioneering to bring about a  new way of learning in the campus. NIT SIKKIM has continuously bridged academics and extra-curricular activities by organising events. These events enable the students to hone their skills and talents to evolve.
</string>

    <string name="title_activity_image_viewer">ImageViewerActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guest_description">GuestDescriptionActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sponsors">SponsorsActivity</string>

</resources>
